Guide to the Archives of the Soviet communist party and Soviet state microfilm collection: Russian State Archives of Social and Political History (Rossiiskii gosudarstvennyi arkhiv sotsialno-politicheskoi istorii - RGASPI)
Hoover Institution Archives
- Fond 17, The Central Committee of the Communist Party of the Soviet Union records, 1903-1965; 1971; 2,457 reels
  - Opis 139: Department for Organizational and Party Work Information Sector, 1971, 210 reels) (Reel 2.900-2.940, Reel 2.1213-2.1381)
    - Protocols nos. 11-20 of the meetings of the Bureau of Ivanovskii obkom; protocols nos. 36-37 and 1-14 of the Secretariat of Ivanovskii obkom; protocol and verbatim record of the meeting of party activists of the KPSS organizations of the oblast and city of Ivanovo; protocol and verbatim record of the meeting of party activists of the KPSS organizations of the oblast of Ivanovo; protocol and verbatim record of the 20th conference of the KPSS organization of the city of Ivanovo; protocols nos. 16 and 1-4 and verbatim records of the plenary sessions of Ivanovskii gorkom; protocols nos. 1-9 of the meetings of the Bureau of Ivanovskii gorkom (Reel 2.1220, File 314-321)
    - Protocols nos. 10-20 of the meetings of the Bureau of Ivanovskii gorkom; protocols nos. 1-2 and verbatim record of the meeting of party activists of the KPSS organization of the city of Ivanovo; protocol and verbatim record of the 17th conference of the KPSS organization of the oblast of Irkutsk; protocols and verbatim records of the 11th, 1st, 2nd, and 3rd plenary sessions of Irkutskii obkom; protocols nos. 84-87 of the meetings of the Bureau of Irkutskii obkom (Reel 2.1221, File 322-329)
    - Protocols nos. 88 and 1-23 of the meetings of the Bureau of Irkutskii obkom (Reel 2.1222, File 330-334)
    - Protocols nos. 17 and 1-4 of the meetings of the Secretariat of Irkutskii obkom; protocol and verbatim record of the meeting of party activists of the KPSS organizations of the city and oblast of Irkutsk; verbatim record of the 17th conference of the KPSS organization of the city of Irkutsk; protocols nos. 1-5 of the plenary sessions of Irkutskii gorkom; protocols nos. 61 and 1-20 of the meetings of the Bureau of Irkutskii gorkom (Reel 2.1223, File 335-341)
    - Protocols nos. 1-2 of the meetings of party activists of the KPSS organizations of the city of Irkutsk; protocol and verbatim record of the 31st conference of the KPSS organization of Kabrdino-Balkaria; protocols nos. 13 and 1-4 of the plenary sessions of Kabardino-Balkarskii obkom; protocols nos. 71-73 and 1-14 of the meetings of the Bureau of Kabardino-Balkarskii obkom (Reel 2.1224, File 342-352)
    - Protocols nos. 15-22 of the meetings of the Bureau of Kabardino-Balkarskii obkom; protocols nos. 28 and 1-12 of the meetings of the Secretariat of Kabardino-Balkarskii obkom; protocol no. 1 of the meeting of party activists of the KPSS organization of Kabardino-Balkaria; protocol no. 2 and protocol no. 3 with verbatim record of the meetings of party activists of the KPSS organizations of Kabardino-Balkaria and the city of Nalchik; protocol and verbatim record of the conference of the KPSS organization of the city of Nalchik; protocols nos. 16 and 1-5 of the plenary sessions of Nalchikskii gorkom (Reel 2.1225, File 353-361)
    - Protocols nos. 105 and 1-27 of the meetings of the Bureau of Nalchikskii gorkom (Reel 2.1226, File 362-366)
    - Protocols nos. 28-31 of the meetings of the Bureau of Nalchikskii gorkom; protocols nos. 1 and 2 of the meeting of party activists of the KPSS organization of the city of Nalchik; protocol and verbatim record of the 13th conference of the KPSS organization of the oblast of Kaliningrad; protocols nos. 13 and 1-3 and verbatim records of the plenary sessions of Kaliningradskii obkom; protocols nos. 55-57 and 1-4 of the meetings of the Bureau of Kaliningradskii obkom (Reel 2.1227, File 367-374)
    - Protocols nos. 5-16 of the meetings of the Bureau of Kaliningradskii obkom; protocols nos. 36-77 and 1-10 of the meetings of the Secretariat of Kaliningradskii obkom; protocols and verbatim records of the meetings of party activists of the KPSS organization of the oblast of Kaliningrad; protocol of the 14th conference of the KPSS organization of the city of Kaliningrad; protocols nos. 14 and 1-5 and verbatim records of the plenary sessions of Kaliningradskii gorkom; protocols nos. 42-43 and 1-6 of the meetings of the Bureau of Kaliningradskii gorkom (Reel 2.1228, File 375-383)
    - Protocols nos. 6 (cont.) and 7-15 of the meetings of the Bureau of Kaliningradskii gorkom; protocol and verbatim record of the 19th conference of the KPSS organization of the oblast of Kalinin; protocols nos. 14 and 1-4 and verbatim records of the plenary sessions of Kalininskii obkom; protocols nos. 90-92 and 1-12 of the meetings of the Bureau of Kalininskii obkom (Reel 2.1229, File 383-393)
    - Protocols nos. 12 (cont.) and 13-24 of the meetings of the Bureau of Kalininskii obkom; protocols nos. 33-35 and 1-8 of the meetings of the Secretariat of Kalininskii obkom; verbatim records of the meetings of party activists of the KPSS organization of the oblast of Kalinin; protocol of the 22nd conference of the KPSS organization of the city of Kalinin; protocols nos. 7 and 1-5 and verbatim records of the plenary sessions of Kalininskii gorkom; protocols nos. 79 and 1-10 of the meetings of the Bureau of Kalininskii gorkom (Reel 2.1230, File 393-401)
    - Protocols nos. 11-24 of the meetings of the Bureau of Kalininskii gorkom; protocols nos. 1-3 of the meetings of party activists of the KPSS organization of the city of Kalinin; protocol and verbatim record of the 22nd conference of the KPSS organization of Kalmykia; protocols nos. 13 and 1-5 of the plenary sessions of Kalmykskii obkom; verbatim records of the 3rd and 4th plenary sessions of Kalmykskii obkom; protocols nos. 71-74 and 1 of the meetings of the Bureau of Kalmykskii obkom (Reel 2.1231, File 402-409)
    - Protocols nos. 2-23 of the meetings of the Bureau of Kalmykskii obkom; protocols nos. 16 and 1-10 of the meetings of the Secretariat of Kalmykskii obkom; protocol no. 1 and verbatim record of the meeting of party activists of the KPSS organizations of Kalmykia and the city of Elista; verbatim record of the meeting of party activists of the KPSS organizations of Kalmykia; protocol of the 12th conference of the KPSS organization of the city of Elista (Reel 2.1232, File 410-418)
    - Protocol of the 12th conference of the KPSS organization of the city of Elista (cont.); protocols nos. 16 and 1-5 of the plenary sessions of Elistinskii gorkom; protocols nos. 79-80 and 1-18 of the meetings of the Bureau of Elistinskii gorkom (Reel 2.1233, File 418-424)
    - Protocols nos. 19-24 of the meetings of the Bureau of Elistinskii gorkom; protocol and verbatim record of the 14th conference of the KPSS organization of the oblast of Kaluga; protocols nos. 12 and 1-3 of the plenary sessions of Kaluzhskii obkom; protocols nos. 37 and 1-7 of the meetings of the Bureau of Kaluzhskii obkom (Reel 2.1234, File 424-430)
    - Protocols nos. 7 (cont.) and 8-11 of the meetings of the Bureau of Kaluzhskii obkom; protocols nos. 29 and 1-9 of the meetings of the Secretariat of Kaluzhskii obkom; protocol nos. 1-2 of the meetings of party activists of the KPSS organizations of the oblast and the city of Kaluga; protocol of the 21st conference of the KPSS organization of the city of Kaluga; protocols nos. 1-4 of the plenary sessions of Kaluzhskii gorkom; protocols nos. 1-3 of the meetings of the Bureau of Kaluzhskii gorkom (Reel 2.1235, File 430-437)
    - Protocols nos. 4-26 of the meetings of the Bureau of Kaluzhskii gorkom (Reel 2.1236, File 438-443)
    - Protocols of the meeting of party activists of the KPSS organization of the city of Kaluga and of the ceremonial meeting honoring the 600th anniversary and the Order of Labor Red Banner awarded to the city of Kaluga; protocol and verbatim record of the 17th conference of the KPSS organization of the oblast of Kamchatka; protocols nos. 11-12 and 1-3 of the plenary sessions of Kamchatskii obkom; verbatim records of the 2nd and 3rd plenary sessions of Kamchatskii obkom; protocols nos. 75, 77, and 1-6 of the meetings of the Bureau of Kamchatskii obkom (Reel 2.1237, File 444-451)
    - Protocols nos. 7-23 of the meetings of the Bureau of Kamchatskii obkom; protocols nos. 36-37 and 1-14 of the meetings of the Secretariat of Kamchatskii obkom; verbatim records of the July and August meetings of party activists of the KPSS organization of the oblast of Kamachatka (Reel 2.1238, File 541-458)
    - Verbatim record of the December meeting of party activists of the KPSS organization of the oblast of Kamachatka; protocol and verbatim record of the 25th conference of the KPSS organization of the city of Petropavlovsk; protocols nos. 13 and 1-4 of the plenary sessions of Petropavlovskii gorkom; protocols nos. 93 and 1-25 of the meetings of the Bureau of Petropavlovskii gorkom (Reel 2.1239, File 459-465)
    - Protocols nos. 26-31 of the meetings of the Bureau of Petropavlovskii gorkom; protocol of the meeting of party activists of the KPSS organization of the city of Petropavlovsk; protocol and verbatim record of the 28th conference of the KPSS organization of Karelia; protocols nos. 11 and 1-4 and verbatim records of the plenary sessions of Karelskii obkom; protocols nos. 75-78 and 1-4 of the meetings of the Bureau of Karelskii obkom (Reel 2.1240, File 465-471)
    - Protocols nos. 4 (cont.) and 5-22 of the meetings of the Bureau of Karelskii obkom; protocols nos. 30 and 1-8 of the meetings of the Secretariat of Karelskii obkom; protocol and verbatim record of the January meeting of party activists of the KPSS organizations of Karelia and of the city of Petrozavodsk (Reel 2.1241, File 471-478)
    - Verbatim record of the January meeting (cont.) and protocols and verbatim records of the April, August, and December meetings of party activists of the KPSS organizations of Karelia and of the city of Petrozavodsk; protocol and verbatim record of the 36th conference of the KPSS organization of the city of Petrozavodsk; protocols nos. 13 and 1-5 of the plenary sessions of Petrozavodskii gorkom; protocols nos. 1-9 of the meetings of the Bureau of Petrozavodskii gorkom (Reel 2.1242, File 478-483)
    - Protocols nos. 9 (cont.) and 10-24 of the meetings of the Bureau of Petrozavodskii gorkom; protocol and verbatim record of the 14th conference of the KPSS organization of the oblast of Kemerovo; protocols nos. 12 and 1-3 of the plenary sessions of Kemerovskii obkom; verbatim record of the February plenary session of Kemerovskii obkom (Reel 2.1243, File 483-491)
    - Verbatim records of the June and October plenary sessions of Kemerovskii obkom; protocols nos. 75-78 and 1-22 of the meetings of the Bureau of Kemerovskii obkom (Reel 2.1244, File 492-498)
    - Protocols nos. 36-37 and 1-10 of the meetings of the Secretariat of Kemerovskii obkom; protocols nos. 1-2 and verbatim records of the meetings of party activists of the KPSS organization of the oblast of Kemerovo; verbatim record of the 28th conference of the KPSS organization of the city of Kemerovo; protocols nos. 15 and 1-4 of the plenary sessions of Kemerovskii gorkom (Reel 2.1245, File 499-506)
    - Protocols nos. 74 and 1-29 of the meetings of the Bureau of Petrozavodskii gorkom; protocols nos. 1-5 of the meetings of party activists of the KPSS organization of the city of Kemerovo; protocol and verbatim record of the 18th conference of the KPSS organization of the oblast of Kirovsk; protocols nos. 16 and 1-4 of the plenary sessions of Kirovskii obkom; protocols nos. 69-73 and 1-2 of the meetings of the Bureau of Kirovskii obkom (Reel 2.1246, File 507-513)
    - Protocols nos. 2 (cont.) and 3-22 of the meetings of the Bureau of Kirovskii obkom; protocols nos. 43-44 and 1-17 of the meetings of the Secretariat of Kirovskii obkom; protocol and verbatim record of the April meeting of party activists of the KPSS organization of the city of Kirovsk (Reel 2.1247, File 513-519)
    - Verbatim record of the August meeting and protocol of the December meeting of party activists of the KPSS organization of the city of Kirovsk; verbatim record of the 21st conference of the KPSS organization of the city of Kirovsk; protocols nos. 13 and 1-5 of the plenary sessions of Kirovskii gorkom; protocols nos. 67 and 1-18 of the meetings of the Bureau of Kirovskii gorkom; verbatim records of the meetings of representatives of bodies of workers and of leading workers from the enterprises of the city and oblast of Kirovsk; verbatim record of the 30th conference of the KPSS organization of Komi oblast (Reel 2.1248, File 519-525)
    - Verbatim record of the 30th conference of the KPSS organization of Komi oblast (cont.); protocols nos. 13 and 1-4 and verbatim records of the plenary sessions of Komi obkom; protocols nos. 49 and 1-11 of the meetings of the Bureau of Komi obkom (Reel 2.1249, File 525-530)
    - Protocols nos. 11 (cont.) and 12-13 of the meetings of the Bureau of Komi obkom; protocols nos. 25 and 1-8 of the meetings of the Secretariat of Komi obkom; protocols nos. 1 and 2 of the meetings of party activists of the KPSS organizations of the Komi oblast and the city of Syktyvkar; protocol no. 2 of the meeting of party activists of the KPSS organization of the Komi oblast; protocol of the 26th conference of the KPSS organization of the city of Syktyvkar; protocols nos. 15 and 1-4 of the plenary sessions of Syktyvkarskii gorkom; protocols nos. 1-10 of the meetings of the Bureau of Syktyvkarskii gorkom (Reel 2.1250, File 530-538)
    - Protocols nos. 10 (cont.) and 11-13 of the meetings of the Bureau of Syktyvkarskii gorkom; protocols of the meetings of party activists of the KPSS organization of the city of Syktyvkar; protocol and verbatim record of the 14th conference of the KPSS organization of the oblast of Kostroma; protocols nos. 13 and 1-3 of the plenary sessions of Kostromskoi obkom; verbatim records of the 2nd and 3rd plenary sessions of Kostromskoi obkom; protocols nos. 105-106 and 1-4 of the meetings of the Bureau of Kostromskoi obkom (Reel 2.1251, File 538-545)
    - Protocols nos. 5-23 of the meetings of the Bureau of Kostromskoi obkom; protocols nos. 36, 57, and 1-14 of the meetings of the Secretariat of Kostromskoi obkom; protocols nos. 1-3 of the meetings of party activists of the KPSS organizations of the oblast and city of Kostroma; verbatim record of the February meeting of party activists of the KPSS organizations of the oblast and city of Kostroma (Reel 2.1252, File 546-552)
    - Verbatim records of the April and December meetings of party activists of the KPSS organizations of the oblast and city of Kostroma; verbatim record of the 28th conference of the KPSS organization of the city of Kostroma; protocols nos. 14 and 1-5 and verbatim records of the plenary sessions of Kostromskoi gorkom; protocols nos. 1-6 of the meetings of the Bureau of Kostromskoi gorkom (Reel 2.1253, File 553-558)
    - Protocols nos. 6 (cont.) and 7-27 of the meetings of the Bureau of Kostromskoi gorkom (Reel 2.1254, File 558-563)
    - Protocols nos. 24-27 (cont.) of the meetings of the Bureau of Kostromskoi gorkom; protocols nos. 2-4 of the meetings of party activists of the KPSS organization of the city of Kostroma; protocol and verbatim record of the 16th conference of the KPSS organization of Krasnodarskii krai; protocols nos. 15 and 1-6 and verbatim records of the plenary sessions of Krasnodarskii kraikom; protocols nos. 78-82 and 1-2 of the meetings of the Bureau of Krasnodarskii kraikom (Reel 2.1255, File 564-568)
    - Protocols nos. 3-26 of the meetings of the Bureau of Krasnodarskii kraikom; protocols nos. 30 and 1-7 of the meetings of the Secretariat of Krasnodarskii kraikom; protocols nos. 1-2 of the meetings of party activists of the KPSS organization of Krasnodarskii krai; protocol of the 25th conference of the KPSS organization of the city of Krasnodar (Reel 2.1256, File 569-575)
    - Protocol of the 25th conference of the KPSS organization of the city of Krasnodar (cont.); protocols nos. 16 and 1-4 of the plenary sessions of Krasnodarskii gorkom; protocols nos. 75-76 and 1-25 of the meetings of the Bureau of Krasnodarskii gorkom; protocols nos. 1-3 and verbatim records of the meetings of party activists of the KPSS organization of the city of Krasnodar (Reel 2.1257, File 575-581)
    - Protocol of the 23rd conference of the KPSS organization of Adygeia; protocols nos. 13 and 1-5 of the plenary sessions of Adygeiskii obkom; protocols nos. 66 and 1-16 of the meetings of the Bureau of Adygeiskii obkom; protocol of the meeting of party activists of the KPSS organization of Adygeia; verbatim record of the 17th conference of the KPSS organization of Krasnoiarskii krai (Reel 2.1258, File 582-588)
    - Verbatim record of the 17th conference of the KPSS organization of Krasnoiarskii krai (cont.) and of the 1st plenary session of Krasnoiarskii kraikom; protocols of the 4th and 5th and verbatim records of the 2nd, 3rd, and 5th plenary sessions of Krasnoiarskii kraikom; protocols nos. 67-68 and 1-6 of the meetings of the Bureau of Krasnoiarskii kraikom (Reel 2.1259, File 588-594)
    - Protocols nos. 7-19 of the meetings of the Bureau of Krasnoiarskii kraikom; protocols nos. 54-56 and 1-16 of the meetings of the Secretariat of Krasnoiarskii kraikom (Reel 2.1260, File 595-600)
    - Verbatim records of the meetings of party activists of the KPSS organization of Krasnoiarskii krai; protocol and verbatim record of the 27th conference of the KPSS organization of the city of Krasnoiarsk; protocols nos. 14 and 1-5 and verbatim records of the plenary sessions of Krasnoiarskii gorkom; protocols nos. 58-59 and 1-20 of the meetings of the Bureau of Krasnoiarskii gorkom (Reel 2.1261, File 601-607)
    - Protocols nos. 21-23 of the meetings of the Bureau of Krasnoiarskii gorkom; protocols of the meetings of party activists of the KPSS organization of the city of Krasnoiarsk; protocol and verbatim record of the 21st conference of the KPSS organization of Khakassia; protocols nos. 14 and 1-4 and verbatim records of the plenary sessions of Khakasskii obkom; protocols nos. 68 and 1-5 of the meetings of the Bureau of Khakasskii obkom (Reel 2.1262, File 607-612)
    - Protocols nos. 6-20 of the meetings of the Bureau of Khakasskii obkom; protocols nos. 1-10 of the meetings of the Secretariat of Khakasskii obkom; protocols nos. 1 and 2 of the meetings of party activists of the KPSS organization of Khakassia; protocol and verbatim record of the 21st conference of the KPSS organization of the oblast of Kuibyshev (Reel 2.1263, File 613-619)
    - Verbatim record of the 21st conference of the KPSS organization of the oblast of Kuibyshev (cont.); protocols nos. 13 and 1-3 of the plenary sessions of Kuibyshevskii obkom; verbatim record of the 2nd plenary session of Kuibyshevskii obkom; protocols nos. 75-77 and 1-4 of the meetings of the Bureau of Kuibyshevskii obkom (Reel 2.1264, File 619-624)
    - Protocols nos. 5-21 of the meetings of the Bureau of Kuibyshevskii obkom; protocols nos. 29 and 1-6 of the meetings of the Secretariat of Kuibyshevskii obkom; verbatim record of the meeting of party activists of the KPSS organizations of the oblast and city of Kuibyshev (Reel 2.1265, File 625-630)
    - Verbatim records of the meetings of party activists of the KPSS organization of the oblast of Kuibyshev; protocol and verbatim record of the 24th conference of the KPSS organization of the city of Kuibyshev; protocols nos. 14 and 1-4 and verbatim records of the plenary sessions of Kuibyshevskii gorkom; verbatim record of the 2nd plenary session of Kuibyshevskii gorkom; protocols nos. 77-78 and 1-14 of the meetings of the Bureau of Kuibyshevskii gorkom (Reel 2.1266, File 631-640)
    - Protocols nos. 15-22 of the meetings of the Bureau of Kuibyshevskii gorkom; verbatim record of the meeting of party activists of the KPSS organization of the city of Kuibyshev; protocol and verbatim record of the 14th conference of the KPSS organization of the oblast of Kurgan; protocols nos. 14 and 1-3 and verbatim records of the plenary sessions of Kurganskii obkom; protocols nos. 94-98 and 1-11 of the meetings of the Bureau of Kurganskii obkom (Reel 2.1267, File 640-646)
    - Protocols nos. 11 (cont.) and 12-22 of the meetings of the Bureau of Kurganskii obkom; protocols nos. 65-68 and 1-18 of the meetings of the Secretariat of Kurganskii obkom; protocols and verbatim records of the meetings of party activists of the KPSS organization of the oblast of Kurgan; protocol and verbatim record of the 18th conference of the KPSS organization of the city of Kurgan; protocols nos. 14 and 1-4 and verbatim records of the plenary sessions of Kurganskii gorkom (Reel 2.1268, File 646-651)
    - Protocols nos. 76-78 and 1-16 of the meetings of the Bureau of Kurganskii gorkom; protocols and verbatim records of the meetings of party activists of the KPSS organization of the city of Kurgan; protocol and verbatim record of the 17th conference of the KPSS organization of the oblast of Kursk; protocols nos. 15 and 1-4 and verbatim records of the plenary sessions of Kurskii obkom; verbatim record of the 3rd plenary session of Kurskii obkom (Reel 2.1269, File 652-659)
    - Verbatim record of the 4th plenary session of Kurskii obkom; protocols nos. 79-83 and 1-20 of the meetings of the Bureau of Kurskii obkom (Reel 2.1270, File 660-665)
    - Protocols nos. 20 (cont.) and 21-23 of the meetings of the Bureau of Kurskii obkom; protocols nos. 21 and 1-6 of the meetings of the Secretariat of Kurskii obkom; verbatim records of the meetings of party activists of the KPSS organization of the oblast of Kursk; protocol of the 17th conference of the KPSS organization of the city of Kursk; protocols nos. 14 and 1-4 of the plenary sessions of Kurskii gorkom; protocols nos. 65 and 1-5 of the meetings of the Bureau of Kurskii gorkom (Reel 2.1271, File 665-672)
    - Protocols nos. 6-21 of the meetings of the Bureau of Kurskii gorkom; protocols nos. 1-2 of the meetings of party activists of the KPSS organization of the city of Kursk; protocol and verbatim record of the conference of the KPSS organization of the oblast of Leningrad; protocols nos. 13-14 and 1-2 of the plenary sessions of Leningradskii obkom; protocol and verbatim record of the 3rd plenary session of Leningradskii obkom (Reel 2.1272, File 673-678)
    - Verbatim record (cont.) of the 3rd plenary session of Leningradskii obkom; protocols nos. 91-93 and 1-18 of the meetings of the Bureau of Leningradskii obkom; protocols nos. 1-5 of the meetings of the Secretariat of Leningradskii obkom (Reel 2.1273, File 678-683)
    - Verbatim records of the meetings of party activists of the KPSS organization of the oblast of Leningrad; protocol and verbatim record of the conference of the KPSS organization of the city of Leningrad; protocols nos. 14-15 and 1-3 of the plenary sessions of Leningradskii gorkom; protocols nos. 78-81 and 1-12 of the meetings of the Bureau of Leningradskii gorkom (Reel 2.1274, File 684-688)
    - Protocols nos. 13-22 of the meetings of the Bureau of Leningradskii gorkom; protocol and verbatim record of the 10th conference of the KPSS organization of the oblast of Lipetsk; protocols nos. 13 and 1-4 and verbatim records of the plenary sessions of Lipetskii obkom; protocols nos. 58 and 1-2 of the meetings of the Bureau of Lipetskii obkom (Reel 2.1275, File 689-694)